<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Notes on r4sso.github.io</title>
    <link>https://r4sso.github.io/notes/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Notes on r4sso.github.io</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://r4sso.github.io/notes/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Site Development</title>
      <link>https://r4sso.github.io/notes/dev-todo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://r4sso.github.io/notes/dev-todo/</guid>
      <description>Todo Optimize images (Convert to WebP) Reduce fonts file size Search without JS? (Maybe) Fix need to refresh to change comment theme Fix code copy button (29-09-2023)
Images Optimization (28-09-2023)
Search fix. Notes/Categories styling. Simplified featured.html. Add recent posts to home. Folder structure. (27-09-2023)
Iosevka fonts added (d5519ca). Head title order. New front matter if comment:false disable giscus. Comment moved inside article. Seperator removed from navbar. Gallery added to navbar. avatar added in /about &amp;amp; styling change.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Git</title>
      <link>https://r4sso.github.io/notes/git/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 02:11:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://r4sso.github.io/notes/git/</guid>
      <description>Create a new repository on the command line echo &amp;#34;# Something&amp;#34; &amp;gt;&amp;gt; README.md git init git add README.md git commit -m &amp;#34;first commit&amp;#34; git branch -M main git remote add origin https://github.com/[username]/[repo].git git push -u origin main Push an existing repository from the command line git remote add origin https://github.com/[username]/[repo].git git branch -M main git push -u origin main Common Problem Notes to troubleshoot
Contributions not showing on profile Make sure your config is match</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arch Linux: Cleanup</title>
      <link>https://r4sso.github.io/notes/arch-cleanup/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://r4sso.github.io/notes/arch-cleanup/</guid>
      <description>Clean pkg cache List packages
ls /var/cache/pacman/pkg/ | less Remove all pkg except those installed
sudo pacman -Sc Remove all files
sudo pacman -Scc Or with yay
yay -Scc Remove unused packages List unused
sudo pacman -Qtdq Remove unused
sudo pacman -R $(pacman -Qtdq) Journal logs sudo journalctl --vacuum-time=2d This will remove log older than 2 days, you can change accordingly. Clear journal log older than x day/month/year sudo journalctl --vacuum-size=100M Restrict logs to a certain size Clean home cache cache is located in ~/.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tools</title>
      <link>https://r4sso.github.io/notes/tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://r4sso.github.io/notes/tools/</guid>
      <description>Useful tools for Pentest | CTF
Forensics Summary
Title - tools name Description - what the tools for CTF - Usefulness for CTF Title Description CTF exiftool meta information reader/writer Clues / flags strings Useful for finding clues foremost Recover files based on their headers, footers, and internal data structures data carving steghide </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>links</title>
      <link>https://r4sso.github.io/notes/links/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://r4sso.github.io/notes/links/</guid>
      <description>Collection of links.
Title Description GTFOBins A curated list of Unix binaries that can be exploited by an attacker to bypass local security restrictions CyberChef A s1imple, intuitive web app for carrying out all manner of &amp;ldquo;cyber&amp;rdquo; operations within a web browser. Payloads All The Things A list of useful payloads and bypass for Web Application Security and Pentest/CTF Books Title Description Anna’s Archive Non-profit, open-source search engine for “shadow libraries”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arch Linux Install (Hyprland)</title>
      <link>https://r4sso.github.io/notes/archinstall/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://r4sso.github.io/notes/archinstall/</guid>
      <description>Installation My arch linux installation.
Archinstall [minimal]: Compositor : Hyprland Terminal : Kitty Bar/Dock : Ags (https://github.com/Aylur/ags) File-manager : Nautilus My dotfiles availabe on (github) **SOON
yay Notes: Run as user NOT ROOT!
git clone https://aur.archlinux.org/yay cd yay makepkg -si Packages FOR NVIDIA: hyprland-nvidia-git
yay -S hyprland aylurs-gtk-shell polkit-gnome neovim viewnior \ pavucontrol sassc swww wl-clipboard wf-recorder brightnessctl \ hyprpicker slurp grimblast wayshot swappy nautilus nerdfonts Configuration Wrapping the launcher #!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
